<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working Groups on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/working-groups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working Groups on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/working-groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</guid>
      <description>Save the Date and Register: SwissRN Annual Meeting and Swiss Reproducibility Awards, 13.1.2023
After we had to postpone the SwissRN Annual Meeting, it is now scheduled to take place in person on January 13, 2023 in Berne. Please save the date and register here until Friday, 16th December 2022.
Program Highlights: Presentation of the first Swiss Reproducibility Award Keynote by Brian Nosek, Co-founder and Executive Director of the Center for Open Science Discussion of the SwissRN Strategy Framework</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initiatives</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Preregistration and Registered Reports Research Assessment and Incentives Replication Studies Research Methodology Training Computational Reproducibility ReproducibiliTea
Preregistration and Registered Reports Preregistration, or the practice of documenting research aspects such as hypothesis, sample size, design, data exclusion, and statistical analyses, before data collection or data analysis, can help reduce questionable research practices. When integrated into the publishing process in the form of Registered Reports, it can also reduce publication bias.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</guid>
      <description>The first SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place on October 1st, 2021. The day before leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting.
If you are working in or close to research in Switzerland and would like to participate, please register for the meeting through this link (deadline September 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Launch Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</guid>
      <description>On October 23rd, 2020 the Swiss Reproducibility Network had its official (virtual) launch meeting. Members of the advisory board and of other Reproducibility Networks and stakeholders presented their vision on the reproducibility of research. A lively discussion of view points and potential action points inspired the more informal afternoon in which SwissRN defined its future activities.
Working groups have been formed on
Preregistration and Registered Reports: initial leader Evie Vergauwe Research Assessment and Incentives: initial leader Eva Furrer Replication Studies: initial leader Leonhard Held Research Methodology: initial leader Hanno Würbel Courses and course materials: initial leader Simon Schwab Journal club and communication: initial leader Eva Furrer More details on the working groups will be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
