<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working Groups on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/working-groups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working Groups on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/working-groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Initiatives</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Open Research Data Preregistration and Registered Reports Research Assessment and Incentives Replication Studies Research Methodology Training Computational Reproducibility ReproducibiliTea
Open Research Data In order to reproduce and replicate research findings, open and also FAIR research data are a prerequisite. However, publishing research data is still not a standard and studies show how difficult it is to gain access to research data upon request. The SwissRN working group aims to promote open research data, to improve and facilitate data management across different research disciplines, to provide a network to collaborate in Open Research Data projects (including project proposals for ORD calls) and to engage with different stakeholders to facilitate dissemination and uptake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Reproducibility</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/computational/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/computational/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Why Computational Reproducibility? Who we are and how we work Seminar Series
Why Computational Reproducibility? Computational reproducibility is the ability to independently verify the results of a computational study using the same data and methods. It is a critical aspect of scientific research as it ensures the transparency and credibility of scientific findings. Computational reproducibility allows researchers to build upon the work of others, helping to accelerate scientific progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</guid>
      <description>Reminder:
SwissRN Annual Meeting and Swiss Reproducibility Award, 13.1.2023
The SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place in person on January 13, 2023 in Bern. It is a great opportunity to connect and discuss the activities of SwissRN and its future strategy.
Location: University of Bern, Hochschulstrasse 4, Kuppelraum
Program:
Time Topic 09:30-09:40 Welcome Note by VR Research Prof. Hugues Abriel 09:40-10:40 Presentation and Discussion of SwissRN Strategy 10:40-11:00 Coffee break 11:00-11:40 Reports from local nodes and discussion 11:40-12:00 Report SwissRN academy 12:00-13:30 Lunch break 13:30-14:00 Reports from working groups 14:00-14:45 Ceremony Swiss Reproducibility Award 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</guid>
      <description>The first SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place on October 1st, 2021. The day before leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting.
If you are working in or close to research in Switzerland and would like to participate, please register for the meeting through this link (deadline September 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Launch Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</guid>
      <description>On October 23rd, 2020 the Swiss Reproducibility Network had its official (virtual) launch meeting. Members of the advisory board and of other Reproducibility Networks and stakeholders presented their vision on the reproducibility of research. A lively discussion of view points and potential action points inspired the more informal afternoon in which SwissRN defined its future activities.
Working groups have been formed on
Preregistration and Registered Reports: initial leader Evie Vergauwe Research Assessment and Incentives: initial leader Eva Furrer Replication Studies: initial leader Leonhard Held Research Methodology: initial leader Hanno Würbel Courses and course materials: initial leader Simon Schwab Journal club and communication: initial leader Eva Furrer More details on the working groups will be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
