<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workshop on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in workshop on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Academy: Workshop on Quarto and R Markdown</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/dataownershipworkshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/dataownershipworkshop/</guid>
      <description>Panel Discussion: Who Owns the Data? – December 5th 2024, 15:00-17:30, Bern
Recent discussions regarding the reproducibility and efficiency of science have instigated institutions, funders, and publishers to promote or demand more transparency, open data, data sharing and data re-use. As such practices open up questions regarding data ownership, usage rights and responsibilities, the Swiss Reproducibility Network in Bern is organizing a panel discussion, where legal experts and researchers will discuss issues around production and ownership of research data in basic science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preregistration &amp; Data Management Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/preregistrationdatamanagementworkshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/preregistrationdatamanagementworkshop/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Swiss Open Research Data Grants, the Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is organizing two half-day workshops for researchers in all empirical disciplines and at all levels at SwissRN institutional members in Switzerland: one about preregistration and registered reports (presented by Evie Vergauwe and Caro Hautekiet) and one about data and research management (presented by Eva Furrer and Rachel Heyard).
The half-day workshops will be held on the same day at four different locations: the University of Zurich and ETH Zurich (May 6th), the University of Bern (May 31st) and the University of Geneva (June 7th).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
