<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Organisation on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/categories/organisation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organisation on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/categories/organisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nodes</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/nodes/</guid>
      <description>Local Node Leaders Local Node Activities How to join
Local Nodes of the SwissRN build the backbone of the network by initiating and coordinating activities at universities and other research institutions. Activities of local nodes are manifold, e.g.
 open research working groups, ReproducibiliTea journal clubs, organisation of training activities such as carpentries workshops, grant and ethics peer review groups etc.  The organisation of local nodes differs from institution to institutions from a formalized administration to informal grassroot groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/organisation/</guid>
      <description>Steering Committee Institutions Stakeholders Advisory Board Coordinator
Steering Committee The steering committee is responsible for the overall coordination of SwissRN activity and strategy.
   Institution Unit Name      University of Zurich Faculty of Science and Faculty of Medicine, Center for Reproducible Science Leonhard Held    University of Geneva Faculty of Psychology and Educational Sciences, Swiss Open Psychological Science Initiative Evie Vergauwe    University of Bern Vetsuisse Faculty Bern, Swiss 3R Competence Centre Hanno Würbel      Institutions  Member institutions of the SwissRN have formally committed to support the aims of SwissRN and have started their implementation at the institution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
