<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetings on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/meetings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetings on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</guid>
      <description>The first SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place on October 1st, 2021. The day before leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting.
Preliminary meeting schedule:
   Time Topic     9:00-10:00 Report from the European Reproducibility Networks Summit   10:00-11:00 Keynote lecture (E.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swiss Reproducibility Network - many fields, different voices</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</guid>
      <description>The SwissRN is a grassroots movement – everybody can participate, no matter the field they work in, no matter if they are from a big or a small university or from another institution within academia, no matter if they are senior or junior. The common ground of these diverse researchers is the desire to increase reproducibility of research. The goal of the network is to benefit from diversity, to push for trustworthiness from the bottom up, and, quite simply, to promote a culture change towards a focus on quality rather than novelty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Launch Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</guid>
      <description>On October 23rd, 2020 the Swiss Reproducibility Network had its official (virtual) launch meeting. Members of the advisory board and of other Reproducibility Networks and stakeholders presented their vision on the reproducibility of research. A lively discussion of view points and potential action points inspired the more informal afternoon in which SwissRN defined its future activities.
Working groups have been formed on
 Preregistration and Registered Reports: initial leader Evie Vergauwe Research Assessment and Incentives: initial leader Eva Furrer Replication Studies: initial leader Leonhard Held Research Methodology: initial leader Hanno Würbel Courses and course materials: initial leader Simon Schwab Journal club and communication: initial leader Eva Furrer  More details on the working groups will be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>