<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>conference on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in conference on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024: Registration is open now!</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024registration/</guid>
      <description>Swiss Reproducibility Conference Program is online now! Register for the conference until 27th May 2024
The Swiss Reproducibility Network and the Swiss National Science Foundation organize the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference, taking place in Zurich on 10-11 June 2024. Register now for this first national conference that covers topics related to reproducibility and includes the National Reproducibility Awards ceremony.
The two-day conference includes sessions, a hackathon and workshops on reproducibility, replicability, transparency and open scholarship, as well as on meta-research and research assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extension of Call for Abstracts for Swiss Reproducibility Conference and Nominations for Swiss Reproducibility Award 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/extensioncall_srconference_award2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/extensioncall_srconference_award2024/</guid>
      <description>We extended the deadline to submit abstracts for the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference and nominations for the Early Career Researcher Award and Team Award 2024. Don’t miss this last opportunity to present next to our keynote speakers:
Tim Errington, Center for Open Science Anne-Laure Boulesteix, University München Iolanda Pensa, University of Applied Sciences and Arts of Southern Switzerland Christopher Chambers, Cardiff University Sarah de Rijcke, Leiden University Tracey Weissgerber, Berlin Institute of Health at Charité, QUEST Center for Responsible Research You can find all details about the calls on the conference website reproducibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Swiss Reproducibility Award and Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/callforswissreproducibilityawardandswissreproducibilityconference2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/callforswissreproducibilityawardandswissreproducibilityconference2024/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss National Science Foundation and the Swiss Reproducibility Network invite you to submit abstracts for the Swiss Reproducibility Conference, taking place June, 10 - 11, 2024 in Zürich, as well as nominations for the Swiss Reproducibility Award 2024.
First Swiss Reproducibility Conference: Call for Contributed Talks and Posters Don’t miss the opportunity to present your work at the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference that takes place June 10 - 11, 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the date: Swiss Reproducibility Conference, June 10 - 11, 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss National Science Foundation (SNSF) and the Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) co-organise the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference, which takes place 10 - 11 June 2024 in Zürich.
Reproducibility represents an extraordinary challenge for the entire research community. The aim of the conference is to bring together world-leading experts in the field of reproducible research with researchers from all career levels, including early career researchers, and from all disciplines to engage with and learn from each other how to make research more rigorous, transparent and reproducible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
