<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024: Presentations</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024presentations/</guid>
      <description>Presentations from the Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024 Now Available Online!
A big thank you to everyone who participated, presented and engaged in discussions on reproducibility at the inaugural Swiss Reproducibility Conference last June. If you’d like to revisit the insights shared during the event, the presentations are now accessible on OSF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winners of the Swiss Reproducibility Awards 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2024winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2024winners/</guid>
      <description>The winners of the Swiss Reproducibility Awards 2024 were announced at the Swiss Reproducibility Conference at the award ceremony. The prize money of CHF 3000 for each of the Early Career Researcher Awards and the CHF 6000 for the recipients of the team Award was sponsored by the SNSF.
The Early Career Researchers Awards were presented for the second time. The following applicants won this year:
Category Biology and Medicine: Virginia Chiocchia, PhD from the University of Bern for her tool ROB-MEN, a user-friendly web application to assess the Risk Of Bias due to Missing Evidence in Network meta-analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024: Registration is open now!</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024registration/</guid>
      <description>Swiss Reproducibility Conference Program is online now! Register for the conference until 27th May 2024
The Swiss Reproducibility Network and the Swiss National Science Foundation organize the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference, taking place in Zurich on 10-11 June 2024. Register now for this first national conference that covers topics related to reproducibility and includes the National Reproducibility Awards ceremony.
The two-day conference includes sessions, a hackathon and workshops on reproducibility, replicability, transparency and open scholarship, as well as on meta-research and research assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy meets Cancer Research Network Bern</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academymeetsordbern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academymeetsordbern/</guid>
      <description>As a new member of the Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy, I saw an opportunity to turn one of my scheduled presentations at the Cancer Research Network Bern into a small SwissRN Academy event. For this, we reached out to the Open Science Team from the University Library of Bern, who were kind enough to collaborate with us in that manner. We are thus proud to present:
Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy meets Cancer Research Network Bern</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preregistration &amp; Data Management Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/preregistrationdatamanagementworkshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/preregistrationdatamanagementworkshop/</guid>
      <description>As part of the Swiss Open Research Data Grants, the Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is organizing two half-day workshops for researchers in all empirical disciplines and at all levels at SwissRN institutional members in Switzerland: one about preregistration and registered reports (presented by Evie Vergauwe and Caro Hautekiet) and one about data and research management (presented by Eva Furrer and Rachel Heyard).
The half-day workshops will be held on the same day at four different locations: the University of Zurich and ETH Zurich (May 6th), the University of Bern (May 31st) and the University of Geneva (June 7th).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extension of Call for Abstracts for Swiss Reproducibility Conference and Nominations for Swiss Reproducibility Award 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/extensioncall_srconference_award2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/extensioncall_srconference_award2024/</guid>
      <description>We extended the deadline to submit abstracts for the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference and nominations for the Early Career Researcher Award and Team Award 2024. Don’t miss this last opportunity to present next to our keynote speakers:
Tim Errington, Center for Open Science Anne-Laure Boulesteix, University München Iolanda Pensa, University of Applied Sciences and Arts of Southern Switzerland Christopher Chambers, Cardiff University Sarah de Rijcke, Leiden University Tracey Weissgerber, Berlin Institute of Health at Charité, QUEST Center for Responsible Research You can find all details about the calls on the conference website reproducibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Swiss Reproducibility Award and Swiss Reproducibility Conference 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/callforswissreproducibilityawardandswissreproducibilityconference2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/callforswissreproducibilityawardandswissreproducibilityconference2024/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss National Science Foundation and the Swiss Reproducibility Network invite you to submit abstracts for the Swiss Reproducibility Conference, taking place June, 10 - 11, 2024 in Zürich, as well as nominations for the Swiss Reproducibility Award 2024.
First Swiss Reproducibility Conference: Call for Contributed Talks and Posters Don’t miss the opportunity to present your work at the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference that takes place June 10 - 11, 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ReproSeminar with Prof Nicolas Langer @UZH, 06.12.2023</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproseminarprofnicolaslanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproseminarprofnicolaslanger/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a talk by Prof Dr Nicolas Langer on December 6th, 4pm CET, at UZH and online.
The speaker will share his experience with open science, its challenges and advantages, and how it shapes his career. He will also share his tips regarding reproducibility and how he encourages open science in his lab.
More info below and in the flyer.
Title: &amp;ldquo;Bringing Open and Reproducible Science into a Successful Career&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the date: Swiss Reproducibility Conference, June 10 - 11, 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityconference2024/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss National Science Foundation (SNSF) and the Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) co-organise the first Swiss Reproducibility Conference, which takes place 10 - 11 June 2024 in Zürich.
Reproducibility represents an extraordinary challenge for the entire research community. The aim of the conference is to bring together world-leading experts in the field of reproducible research with researchers from all career levels, including early career researchers, and from all disciplines to engage with and learn from each other how to make research more rigorous, transparent and reproducible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Award 2024</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2024/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss National Science Foundation (SNSF) and the Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) joined forces to launch the Swiss Reproducibility Awards 2024. With the goal of supporting and highlighting the work of early career researchers as well as research teams who are paying special attention to rigour, transparency and reproducibility in their research, the SNSF and the SwissRN invite nominations for the Swiss Reproducibility Award. The call will be published early December, so stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Network Anlass @ZHAW, 22.11.2023  </title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilitynetworkevent_zhaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilitynetworkevent_zhaw/</guid>
      <description>Das Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) und das Departement Gesundheit der ZHAW laden interessierte Forschende zu einem Infoanlass ein. SwissRN wird das Netzwerk und seine Aktivitäten vorstellen und aufzeigen, wie sich Forschende bei SwissRN engagieren und vom Netzwerk profitieren können. Danach lernen wir ein SwissRN-Projekt kennen, das von swissuniversities ko-finanziert wird, und bei dem die Wiederverwendbarkeit von Forschungsoutputs im Zentrum steht. Weiter gibt es eine kurze Vorschau auf die erste Schweizer Reproducibility Konferenz, die im Juni 2024 stattfinden wird.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN is now Member of the Coalition for Advancing Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissrnnowamembercoara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissrnnowamembercoara/</guid>
      <description>After SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment in April 2023, we have now also become a member of the Coalition for Advancing Research Assessment (CoARA).
This enables SwissRN members to collaborate in the CoARA Working Groups, currently set up by and allows you to participate in the call to found Working Groups, in case your own university is not a member itself. The call was launched end of March 2023 and will be completed in autumn 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STRIDE Lab Summer School</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/summerschool2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/summerschool2023/</guid>
      <description>“Systematic reviews of animal studies: fostering evidence-based and reproducible preclinical research”, 28 – 31 Aug 2023 The growing biomedical literature requires researchers to have tools for managing data and conducting structured research. A systematic review is a rigorous, structured, and reproducible research summary that allows to map a research field at the start of a project, are a prerequisite for a clinical trial, or are used to assess employed methods within a field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, 5th May 2023: First Findings</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</guid>
      <description>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, May 5th 2023: First Findings
On May 5th 2023 the Bern node of the SwissRN organized a Reproducibility Hackathon. Thirteen people showed up, re-analysing the statistical analyses of pre-registered reports from the Reproducibility Project Cancer Biology. After eight hours of intense code hacking (with decent breaks for pizza and cake), over 60 confirmatory tests have been re-analysed. Participants got the original pre-registration protocol as well as the published data, while they did not see the code and the report of the study outcome published by the authors beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETH Zurich joined SwissRN as an institutional member!</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</guid>
      <description>We are very happy to announce that ETH Zurich has joined SwissRN as an institutional member. Welcome on board, ETH! We are looking forward to the joint collaboration in our network. Prof. Dr. Christian Wolfrum, Vice President Research of ETH Zurich will be the institutional contact person. Dr. Daniel Stekhoven will represent the institution in the SwissRN steering committee and continue as Local Node Leader. He is also the Managing Director of NEXUS Personalized Health Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN has signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment, which sets a shared direction for changes in assessment practices for research, researchers and research performing organizations. The overarching goal is to maximize the quality and impact of research. SwissRN sees the reform of research assessment practices as one key element in order to advance, promote and ensure rigorous research practices.
More information on the agreement and its commitments can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Reproducibility Seminar</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/computationalreproducibilityseminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/computationalreproducibilityseminar/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the SwissRN seminar series on Computational Reproducibility!
In today&amp;rsquo;s world, computational research has become an essential tool for advancing scientific knowledge and discovery. However, the increasing complexity of computational models and the abundance of data available for analysis can make it challenging to reproduce research results. Computational reproducibility is the ability to independently verify the results of a computational study using the same data and methods. It is a critical aspect of scientific research as it ensures the transparency and credibility of scientific findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</guid>
      <description>Reminder:
SwissRN Annual Meeting and Swiss Reproducibility Award, 13.1.2023
The SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place in person on January 13, 2023 in Bern. It is a great opportunity to connect and discuss the activities of SwissRN and its future strategy.
Location: University of Bern, Hochschulstrasse 4, Kuppelraum
Program:
Time Topic 09:30-09:40 Welcome Note by VR Research Prof. Hugues Abriel 09:40-10:40 Presentation and Discussion of SwissRN Strategy 10:40-11:00 Coffee break 11:00-11:40 Reports from local nodes and discussion 11:40-12:00 Report SwissRN academy 12:00-13:30 Lunch break 13:30-14:00 Reports from working groups 14:00-14:45 Ceremony Swiss Reproducibility Award 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Award Winners</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022winners/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is happy to announce the following winners of its Swiss Reproducibility Award:
Category Biology and Medicine: Mathieu Seppey, University of Geneva Category Humanities and Social Science: Co-Winners Caro Hautekiet and Tobia Spampatti, both University of Geneva The winners will be presented with their award at our Annual Meeting on 13.1.2023 in Berne. Join us in Berne to have the pleasure to hear more about their work!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Award</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is a peer-led consortium that aims to promote and ensure rigorous research practices in Switzerland. SwissRN’s special focus is on reproducibility/replicability. With the goal of supporting and highlighting the work of young scholars who are paying special attention to such issues in their work, SwissRN invites nominations for three annual Swiss Reproducibility Awards.
Criteria
One award is granted in each scientific category: Humanities and Social Sciences; Mathematics, Natural and Engineering Sciences; and Biology and Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Academy Reproducibility Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyreprohack2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyreprohack2022/</guid>
      <description>On 20th May 2022, the Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy will host the first national Reproduciblity Hackathon &amp;ndash; Swiss ReproHack &amp;ndash; at the University of Bern.
For information and registration see here https://www.eventbrite.com/e/swiss-reprohack-swiss-reproducibility-network-academy-tickets-300563923787
The number of participants will be limited to 20 (master or PhD students or other interested persons).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Academy </title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyfirstmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyfirstmeeting/</guid>
      <description>The first event of the Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy will take place online on Friday, February 25 from 16:00 to 17:15.
It will be an informal event where we will talk about why reproducibility and open science matter to us/you. We will also discuss future events. The (tentative) program is the following:
16:00 - 16:30 : presentations (from us/you) + discussion 16:30 - 16:50 : networking (getting to know each other) 16:50 - 17:15 : future activities + closing remarks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Reproducibility Summit 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/europeansummit2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/europeansummit2021/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN will host the first European Reproducibility summit on September 30, 2021 at the University of Bern. Leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting on Ocotber 1st.
List of confirmed attendees:
Name Institution Country Roosmarijn Vandenbroucke Ghent University Belgium Andreas Scherer Institute for Molecular Medicine Finland, Helsinki Finland Vootele Voikar University of Helsinki Finland Hans Rocha Ijzerman Université Grenoble Alpes France Christian Fiebach Goethe University Frankfurt Germany Antonia Schrader Helmholtz Association Open Science Office Germany Cristina Zogmeister University of Milan – Bicocca Italy Loek Brinkman UMC Utrecht The Netherlands Daniel Lakens Eindhoven University of Technology The Netherlands Siri Leknes University of Oslo Norway Dan Quintana University of Oslo Norway Katarzyna Jasko Jagiellonian University Poland Susana Magalhaes University od Porto Portugal Alessandra Souza University of Porto Portugal Gustave Nilsonne Karolinska Institutet, Stockholm Sweden Leonhard Held University of Zurich Switzerland Evie Vergauwe University of Geneva Switzerland Hanno Würbel University of Bern Switzerland Marcus Munafo University of Bristol UK </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</guid>
      <description>The first SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place on October 1st, 2021. The day before leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting.
If you are working in or close to research in Switzerland and would like to participate, please register for the meeting through this link (deadline September 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swiss Reproducibility Network - many fields, different voices</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</guid>
      <description>The SwissRN is a grassroots movement – everybody can participate, no matter the field they work in, no matter if they are from a big or a small university or from another institution within academia, no matter if they are senior or junior. The common ground of these diverse researchers is the desire to increase reproducibility of research. The goal of the network is to benefit from diversity, to push for trustworthiness from the bottom up, and, quite simply, to promote a culture change towards a focus on quality rather than novelty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Launch Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</guid>
      <description>On October 23rd, 2020 the Swiss Reproducibility Network had its official (virtual) launch meeting. Members of the advisory board and of other Reproducibility Networks and stakeholders presented their vision on the reproducibility of research. A lively discussion of view points and potential action points inspired the more informal afternoon in which SwissRN defined its future activities.
Working groups have been formed on
Preregistration and Registered Reports: initial leader Evie Vergauwe Research Assessment and Incentives: initial leader Eva Furrer Replication Studies: initial leader Leonhard Held Research Methodology: initial leader Hanno Würbel Courses and course materials: initial leader Simon Schwab Journal club and communication: initial leader Eva Furrer More details on the working groups will be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Negative Data Prize</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/bestnegativedata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/bestnegativedata/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN steering committee member Hanno Würbel is senior author on a publication that has been awarded the Best Negative Data Prize: Evaluation of the effects of space allowance on measures of animal welfare in laboratory mice.
&amp;ldquo;Established in 2018 by the Global Preclinical Data Forum (GPDF) and co-sponsored by CVB, a non-profit research biotech, and the European College of Neuropsychopharmacology (ECNP), the Best Negative Data Prize aims to highlight the value to negative data—or data where the results do not confirm the expected outcomes or original hypotheses—toward advancing knowledge in neuroscience, providing an incentive for preclinical researchers to publish their &amp;ldquo;negative data&amp;rdquo; results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trojan horse paper</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/covaretractionwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/covaretractionwatch/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN member Florian Cova is an author on the retracted paper &amp;ldquo;SARS-CoV-2 was Unexpectedly Deadlier than Push-scooters: Could Hydroxychloroquine be the Unique Solution?&amp;rdquo;.
Shocked? Read what is mentioned on Retraction Watch:
&amp;ldquo;The retraction of a Trojan horse paper on the novel coronavirus has called into question the validity of another article in the same journal which found that hydroxychloroquine is effective against Covid-19.&amp;rdquo;
See also the Retraction Watch website
Florian has talked with radio RTS Info on this story</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Notes</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproducibilitynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproducibilitynotes/</guid>
      <description>The Center for Reproducible Science (CRS) at the University of Zurich publishes a column on Reproducibility in the british-american magazine Significance:
January 2020
April 2020
Special on COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
