<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>openscience on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/openscience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in openscience on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/openscience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, 5th May 2023: First Findings</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</guid>
      <description>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, May 5th 2023: First Findings
On May 5th 2023 the Bern node of the SwissRN organized a Reproducibility Hackathon. Thirteen people showed up, re-analysing the statistical analyses of pre-registered reports from the Reproducibility Project Cancer Biology. After eight hours of intense code hacking (with decent breaks for pizza and cake), over 60 confirmatory tests have been re-analysed. Participants got the original pre-registration protocol as well as the published data, while they did not see the code and the report of the study outcome published by the authors beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETH Zurich joined SwissRN as an institutional member!</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</guid>
      <description>We are very happy to announce that ETH Zurich has joined SwissRN as an institutional member. Welcome on board, ETH! We are looking forward to the joint collaboration in our network. Prof. Dr. Christian Wolfrum, Vice President Research of ETH Zurich will be the institutional contact person. Dr. Daniel Stekhoven will represent the institution in the SwissRN steering committee and continue as Local Node Leader. He is also the Managing Director of NEXUS Personalized Health Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN has signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment, which sets a shared direction for changes in assessment practices for research, researchers and research performing organizations. The overarching goal is to maximize the quality and impact of research. SwissRN sees the reform of research assessment practices as one key element in order to advance, promote and ensure rigorous research practices.
More information on the agreement and its commitments can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
