<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SwissRN</title>
    <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Institutions</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/institutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/institutions/</guid>
      <description>Institutions can join the SwissRN if the senior management formally commits to supporting the aims of the network, identifies a responsible person in the management structure leading their implementation at the institution, e.g. through training programs at all levels.
Institutions More text &amp;hellip;
   Institution Contact Test Test      University of Zurich Contact    University of Geneva Contact      Test CRS UZH     Alice 23     Nina 23      How to join We expect that institutions seeking membership of SwissRN will want to develop capacity to deliver a research improvement strategy, and to work with SwissRN to develop a strategy for ensuring the sustainability of the Network in the medium- and long-term, and to build a community of institutions focused on research improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nodes</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/nodes/</guid>
      <description>Nodes, or Local Networks, provide a mechanism through which the aims of the SwissRN can be promoted within that institution (e.g., by establishing open research working groups, running training workshops, advocating for the wider adoption of best practice within the institution, etc.).
Local Network Leads A Local Network Lead provides the point of contact for SwissRN, and represents a grass-roots network of researchers at that institution. It is intended that these Local Networks will grow, both in number and size, over time, as researchers elect to participate in SwissRN activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/organisation/</guid>
      <description>Test Simon Test. Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stakeholders</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/stakeholders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/stakeholders/</guid>
      <description>Stakeholders who support the SwissRN form the Stakeholder Engagement Group. This ensures that SwissRN activity is aligned with the strategy and activity of the stakeholders, and allows the exchange of ideas. In addition, the relationship between the Stakeholder Engagement Group and the SwissRN provides stakeholders with a mechanism for obtaining feedback on new initiatives from the research community. See Annex 5: Potential Stakeholders in Switzerland.
Stakeholder engagement groups More text &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de
pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://crsuzh.github.io/SwissRN/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>