<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Initiatives</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/initiatives/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Open Research Data Preregistration and Registered Reports Research Assessment and Incentives Replication Studies Research Methodology Training Computational Reproducibility ReproducibiliTea
Open Research Data In order to reproduce and replicate research findings, open and also FAIR research data are a prerequisite. However, publishing research data is still not a standard and studies show how difficult it is to gain access to research data upon request. The SwissRN working group aims to promote open research data, to improve and facilitate data management across different research disciplines, to provide a network to collaborate in Open Research Data projects (including project proposals for ORD calls) and to engage with different stakeholders to facilitate dissemination and uptake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, 5th May 2023: First Findings</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/successful-reproducibility-hackathonmay2023/</guid>
      <description>Successful Reproducibility Hackathon Bern, May 5th 2023: First Findings
On May 5th 2023 the Bern node of the SwissRN organized a Reproducibility Hackathon. Thirteen people showed up, re-analysing the statistical analyses of pre-registered reports from the Reproducibility Project Cancer Biology. After eight hours of intense code hacking (with decent breaks for pizza and cake), over 60 confirmatory tests have been re-analysed. Participants got the original pre-registration protocol as well as the published data, while they did not see the code and the report of the study outcome published by the authors beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Reproducibility</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/computational/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/computational/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Why Computational Reproducibility? Who we are and how we work Seminar Series
Why Computational Reproducibility? Computational reproducibility is the ability to independently verify the results of a computational study using the same data and methods. It is a critical aspect of scientific research as it ensures the transparency and credibility of scientific findings. Computational reproducibility allows researchers to build upon the work of others, helping to accelerate scientific progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETH Zurich joined SwissRN as an institutional member!</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newmemberethz/</guid>
      <description>We are very happy to announce that ETH Zurich has joined SwissRN as an institutional member. Welcome on board, ETH! We are looking forward to the joint collaboration in our network. Prof. Dr. Christian Wolfrum, Vice President Research of ETH Zurich will be the institutional contact person. Dr. Daniel Stekhoven will represent the institution in the SwissRN steering committee and continue as Local Node Leader. He is also the Managing Director of NEXUS Personalized Health Technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organisation</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/organisation/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Steering Committee Institutions Stakeholders Advisory Board Coordinator
Steering Committee The steering committee is responsible for the overall coordination of SwissRN activity and strategy.
Institution Unit Name University of Zurich Faculty of Science and Faculty of Medicine, Center for Reproducible Science Leonhard Held University of Geneva Faculty of Psychology and Educational Sciences, Swiss Open Psychological Science Initiative Evie Vergauwe University of Bern Vetsuisse Faculty Bern, Swiss 3R Competence Centre Hanno Würbel Institutions Member institutions of the SwissRN are formally committed to support the aims of SwissRN and have begun implementing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN has signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment, which sets a shared direction for changes in assessment practices for research, researchers and research performing organizations. The overarching goal is to maximize the quality and impact of research. SwissRN sees the reform of research assessment practices as one key element in order to advance, promote and ensure rigorous research practices.
More information on the agreement and its commitments can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nodes</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/nodes/</guid>
      <description>Go to: Local Node Leaders Local Node Activities Local Node Members How to join
Local Nodes of the SwissRN build the backbone of the network by initiating and coordinating activities at universities and other research institutions. Activities of local nodes are manifold, e.g.
open research working groups ReproducibiliTea journal clubs organisation of training activities such as carpentries workshops grant and ethics peer review groups etc The organisation of local nodes differs from institution to institution: from a formalised administration to informal grassroot groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Reproducibility Seminar</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/computationalreproducibilityseminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/computationalreproducibilityseminar/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the SwissRN seminar series on Computational Reproducibility!
In today&amp;rsquo;s world, computational research has become an essential tool for advancing scientific knowledge and discovery. However, the increasing complexity of computational models and the abundance of data available for analysis can make it challenging to reproduce research results. Computational reproducibility is the ability to independently verify the results of a computational study using the same data and methods. It is a critical aspect of scientific research as it ensures the transparency and credibility of scientific findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN Strategy SwissRN Strategy (Version February 2023)
Terms of Reference Terms of Reference (Version March 2021)
Executive Summary Executive Summary (Version March 2021)
Presentation Slides Presentation slides on OSF
UKRN Open Research Primers The UKRN primer series is designed to introduce a broad audience to important topics in open and reproducible scholarship.
Reproducibility Reports The Royal Netherlands Academy of Arts and Sciences, 2018: Improving Reproducibility in the Empirical Sciences
The National Academies of Science Engineering Medicine, 2019: Reproducibility and Replicability in Science</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bern Local Node News</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202321february/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202321february/</guid>
      <description>Bern Local Node News: Reproducibility Hackathon, May 5th 2023
As a first activity for this year the Bern node of the SwissRN is organizing a Reproducibility Hackathon on May 5th. The aim of the Hackathon is to investigate whether current practice of preregistration does indeed reduce researcher&amp;rsquo;s degrees of freedom to an extent that the analysis of study outcomes becomes reproducible. The Hackathon is a one-day on-site event in Bern (Friday, May 5th; though for students there is a pre-event lecture on May 4th covering principles of reproducibility, pre-registration, open data as well as a recap of mixed effect model analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2022</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2022/</guid>
      <description>Reminder:
SwissRN Annual Meeting and Swiss Reproducibility Award, 13.1.2023
The SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place in person on January 13, 2023 in Bern. It is a great opportunity to connect and discuss the activities of SwissRN and its future strategy.
Location: University of Bern, Hochschulstrasse 4, Kuppelraum
Program:
Time Topic 09:30-09:40 Welcome Note by VR Research Prof. Hugues Abriel 09:40-10:40 Presentation and Discussion of SwissRN Strategy 10:40-11:00 Coffee break 11:00-11:40 Reports from local nodes and discussion 11:40-12:00 Report SwissRN academy 12:00-13:30 Lunch break 13:30-14:00 Reports from working groups 14:00-14:45 Ceremony Swiss Reproducibility Award 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Award Winners</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022winners/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is happy to announce the following winners of its Swiss Reproducibility Award:
Category Biology and Medicine: Mathieu Seppey, University of Geneva Category Humanities and Social Science: Co-Winners Caro Hautekiet and Tobia Spampatti, both University of Geneva The winners will be presented with their award at our Annual Meeting on 13.1.2023 in Berne. Join us in Berne to have the pleasure to hear more about their work!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202211november/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202211november/</guid>
      <description>We have a new Newsletter! Check out the fifth edition of November 2022
You can subscribe to the newsletter by subscribing to our mailing list.
Image credits: Dennis Skley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202205may/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202205may/</guid>
      <description>We have a new Newsletter! Check out the fourth edition of May 2022
You can subscribe to the newsletter by subscribing to our mailing list.
Image credits: Dennis Skley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Reproducibility Award</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissreproducibilityaward2022/</guid>
      <description>The Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) is a peer-led consortium that aims to promote and ensure rigorous research practices in Switzerland. SwissRN’s special focus is on reproducibility/replicability. With the goal of supporting and highlighting the work of young scholars who are paying special attention to such issues in their work, SwissRN invites nominations for three annual Swiss Reproducibility Awards.
Criteria
One award is granted in each scientific category: Humanities and Social Sciences; Mathematics, Natural and Engineering Sciences; and Biology and Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Academy Reproducibility Hackathon</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyreprohack2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyreprohack2022/</guid>
      <description>On 20th May 2022, the Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy will host the first national Reproduciblity Hackathon &amp;ndash; Swiss ReproHack &amp;ndash; at the University of Bern.
For information and registration see here https://www.eventbrite.com/e/swiss-reprohack-swiss-reproducibility-network-academy-tickets-300563923787
The number of participants will be limited to 20 (master or PhD students or other interested persons).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202202february/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202202february/</guid>
      <description>We have a new Newsletter! Check out the third edition of February 2022
You can subscribe to the newsletter by subscribing to our mailing list.
Image credits: Dennis Skley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN academy</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/academy/</guid>
      <description>Organisation and membership The Swiss Reproducibility Network (SwissRN) Academy is a group of Early Career Researchers from Swiss universities who are interested in reproducibility, metascience, good research practices, and transparency. Our goal is improving the quality of science by sharing our knowledge of reproducible research with students and researchers. We want to create a national network among young researchers from various fields and backgrounds, that enables interdisciplinary dialogue and collaboration. **We’d be happy to see our community grow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Academy </title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyfirstmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/academyfirstmeeting/</guid>
      <description>The first event of the Swiss Reproducibility Network Academy will take place online on Friday, February 25 from 16:00 to 17:15.
It will be an informal event where we will talk about why reproducibility and open science matter to us/you. We will also discuss future events. The (tentative) program is the following:
16:00 - 16:30 : presentations (from us/you) + discussion 16:30 - 16:50 : networking (getting to know each other) 16:50 - 17:15 : future activities + closing remarks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Reproducibility Summit 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/europeansummit2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/europeansummit2021/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN will host the first European Reproducibility summit on September 30, 2021 at the University of Bern. Leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting on Ocotber 1st.
List of confirmed attendees:
Name Institution Country Roosmarijn Vandenbroucke Ghent University Belgium Andreas Scherer Institute for Molecular Medicine Finland, Helsinki Finland Vootele Voikar University of Helsinki Finland Hans Rocha Ijzerman Université Grenoble Alpes France Christian Fiebach Goethe University Frankfurt Germany Antonia Schrader Helmholtz Association Open Science Office Germany Cristina Zogmeister University of Milan – Bicocca Italy Loek Brinkman UMC Utrecht The Netherlands Daniel Lakens Eindhoven University of Technology The Netherlands Siri Leknes University of Oslo Norway Dan Quintana University of Oslo Norway Katarzyna Jasko Jagiellonian University Poland Susana Magalhaes University od Porto Portugal Alessandra Souza University of Porto Portugal Gustave Nilsonne Karolinska Institutet, Stockholm Sweden Leonhard Held University of Zurich Switzerland Evie Vergauwe University of Geneva Switzerland Hanno Würbel University of Bern Switzerland Marcus Munafo University of Bristol UK </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Annual Meeting 2021</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/annualmeeting2021/</guid>
      <description>The first SwissRN Annual Meeting will take place on October 1st, 2021. The day before leaders of current and emerging European Reproducibility Networks will meet with the goal of discussing collaboration and coordination. Many of those leaders will stay as guests for the SwissRN Annual Meeting.
If you are working in or close to research in Switzerland and would like to participate, please register for the meeting through this link (deadline September 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202106june/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202106june/</guid>
      <description>We have a new Newsletter! Check out the second edition of June 2021
You can subscribe to the newsletter by subscribing to our mailing list.
Image credits: Dennis Skley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Newsletter</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202104april/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/newsletter202104april/</guid>
      <description>We have a brand new Newsletter! Check out the first edition of April 2021
You can subscribe to the newsletter by subscribing to our mailing list.
Image credits: Dennis Skley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Swiss Reproducibility Network - many fields, different voices</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/voices/</guid>
      <description>The SwissRN is a grassroots movement – everybody can participate, no matter the field they work in, no matter if they are from a big or a small university or from another institution within academia, no matter if they are senior or junior. The common ground of these diverse researchers is the desire to increase reproducibility of research. The goal of the network is to benefit from diversity, to push for trustworthiness from the bottom up, and, quite simply, to promote a culture change towards a focus on quality rather than novelty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN Launch Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/launchmeeting/</guid>
      <description>On October 23rd, 2020 the Swiss Reproducibility Network had its official (virtual) launch meeting. Members of the advisory board and of other Reproducibility Networks and stakeholders presented their vision on the reproducibility of research. A lively discussion of view points and potential action points inspired the more informal afternoon in which SwissRN defined its future activities.
Working groups have been formed on
Preregistration and Registered Reports: initial leader Evie Vergauwe Research Assessment and Incentives: initial leader Eva Furrer Replication Studies: initial leader Leonhard Held Research Methodology: initial leader Hanno Würbel Courses and course materials: initial leader Simon Schwab Journal club and communication: initial leader Eva Furrer More details on the working groups will be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Negative Data Prize</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/bestnegativedata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/bestnegativedata/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN steering committee member Hanno Würbel is senior author on a publication that has been awarded the Best Negative Data Prize: Evaluation of the effects of space allowance on measures of animal welfare in laboratory mice.
&amp;ldquo;Established in 2018 by the Global Preclinical Data Forum (GPDF) and co-sponsored by CVB, a non-profit research biotech, and the European College of Neuropsychopharmacology (ECNP), the Best Negative Data Prize aims to highlight the value to negative data—or data where the results do not confirm the expected outcomes or original hypotheses—toward advancing knowledge in neuroscience, providing an incentive for preclinical researchers to publish their &amp;ldquo;negative data&amp;rdquo; results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trojan horse paper</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/covaretractionwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/covaretractionwatch/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN member Florian Cova is an author on the retracted paper &amp;ldquo;SARS-CoV-2 was Unexpectedly Deadlier than Push-scooters: Could Hydroxychloroquine be the Unique Solution?&amp;rdquo;.
Shocked? Read what is mentioned on Retraction Watch:
&amp;ldquo;The retraction of a Trojan horse paper on the novel coronavirus has called into question the validity of another article in the same journal which found that hydroxychloroquine is effective against Covid-19.&amp;rdquo;
See also the Retraction Watch website
Florian has talked with radio RTS Info on this story</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Notes</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproducibilitynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/reproducibilitynotes/</guid>
      <description>The Center for Reproducible Science (CRS) at the University of Zurich publishes a column on Reproducibility in the british-american magazine Significance:
January 2020
April 2020
Special on COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareacommunication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareacommunication/</guid>
      <description>One of the SwissRN Focus Areas is communication:
Dissemination of new evidence Propagation of best practices Promotion of a culture change What we offer Publications Whitepapers Guidelines </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareaeducation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareaeducation/</guid>
      <description>One of the SwissRN Focus Areas is education:
courses to early career researchers, conception of basic Good Research Practice training modules for Bachelor and Master students, preparation of online materials; coordination of virtual seminars and journals clubs What we offer Teaching/training materials ReproducibiliTeas CH-wide Workshops Seminars </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformation</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareatransformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/focusareatransformation/</guid>
      <description>One of the SwissRN Focus Areas is transformation:
Research improvement measures and related policies will be designed and evaluated in collaboration with stakeholders. Together we aim to order to influence policy and policy makers towards the improvement of the quality and robustness of research by reforming culture and practice.
What we offer Network to intiate collaboration projects Leverage of a nationwide network with close connection to key players </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
