<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoARA on SwissRN</title>
    <link>http://www.swissrn.org/tags/coara/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CoARA on SwissRN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.swissrn.org/tags/coara/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN is now Member of the Coalition for Advancing Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissrnnowamembercoara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/swissrnnowamembercoara/</guid>
      <description>After SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment in April 2023, we have now also become a member of the Coalition for Advancing Research Assessment (CoARA).
This enables SwissRN members to collaborate in the CoARA Working Groups, currently set up by and allows you to participate in the call to found Working Groups, in case your own university is not a member itself. The call was launched end of March 2023 and will be completed in autumn 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwissRN has signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment</title>
      <link>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.swissrn.org/news/agreementonreformingresearchassessment/</guid>
      <description>SwissRN signed the Agreement on Reforming Research Assessment, which sets a shared direction for changes in assessment practices for research, researchers and research performing organizations. The overarching goal is to maximize the quality and impact of research. SwissRN sees the reform of research assessment practices as one key element in order to advance, promote and ensure rigorous research practices.
More information on the agreement and its commitments can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
